Alan Freed Collection ARC.0006
Library and Archives
- Series I: Financial Records [RESTRICTED], 1943-1967, undated
  - Subseries 10: Fabian Theatres Corporation – Brooklyn Fox Theatre, 1959
    - Accounting, 1959 January 3-1959 April 7
      - Doorman's report, 1959 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 5)
      - Hourly reports of ticket sales, 1959 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 6)
      - Petty cash voucher for Bonaire Music, Inc., 1959 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 7)
      - Cashier's proof sheet, 1959 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 8)
      - Daily box office statements, 1959 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 9)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 10)
      - Hourly reports of ticket sales, 1959 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 11)
      - Petty cash voucher for Bonaire Music, Inc., 1959 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 12)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 13)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 14)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 15)
      - Hourly reports of ticket sales, 1959 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 16)
      - Petty cash voucher for Bonaire Music, Inc., 1959 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 17)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 18)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 19)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 20)
      - Hourly reports of ticket sales, 1959 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 21)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 22)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 23)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 24)
      - Hourly reports of ticket sales, 1959 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 25)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 26)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 April 31 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 27)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 28)
      - Hourly reports of ticket sales, 1959 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 29)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 30)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 31)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 32)
      - Hourly reports of ticket sales, 1959 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 33)
      - Petty cash voucher for Bonaire Music, Inc., 1959 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 34)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 35)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 36)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 37)
      - Hourly reports of ticket sales, 1959 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 38)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 39)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 40)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 41)
      - Hourly reports of ticket sales, 1959 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 42)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 43)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 44)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 45)
      - Hourly reports of ticket sales, 1959 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 46)
      - Petty cash voucher for Bonaire Music, Inc., 1959 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 47)
      - Check #72557A - Bonaire Music, Inc., 1959 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 48)
    - Accounting, 1959 September
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 September 4 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 1)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 September 4 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 2)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 September 4 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 3)
      - Hourly report of ticket sales, 1959 September 4 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 4)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 September 5 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 5)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 September 5 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 6)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 September 5 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 7)
      - Hourly report of ticket sales, 1959 September 5 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 8)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 9)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 10)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 11)
      - Hourly report of ticket sales, 1959 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 12)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 September 7 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 13)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 September 7 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 14)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 September 7 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 15)
      - Hourly report of ticket sales, 1959 September 7 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 16)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 September 8 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 17)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 September 8 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 18)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 September 8 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 19)
      - Hourly report of ticket sales, 1959 September 8 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 20)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 21)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 22)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 23)
      - Hourly report of ticket, 1959 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 24)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 25)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 26)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 27)
      - Hourly report of ticket sales, 1959 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 28)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 29)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 30)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 31)
      - Hourly report of ticket sales, 1959 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 32)
      - Cashier's proof sheets, 1959 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 33)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 34)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 35)
      - Hourly report of ticket sales, 1959 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 36)
      - Cashier's proof sheet, 1959 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 37)
      - Daily box office statement, 1959 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 38)
      - Doorman's report, 1959 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 39)
      - Hourly report of ticket sales, 1959 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 40)
    - Contracts and correspondence, 1959 February-1959 August
      - Agreement between Bonaire Music, Inc. and Fabian Theatre Corporation, 1959 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 18, Object 1)
      - From Jack Hooke to E. L. Fabian, 1959 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 18, Object 2)
      - From Jack Hooke to Philip F. Harling, 1959 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 18, Object 3)
      - Agreement between Bonaire Music, Inc. and Fabian Theatre Corporation, 1959 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 18, Object 4)
      - From Jack Hooke to E. L. Fabian, 1959 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 18, Object 5)
      - From Jack Hooke to Edward L. Fabian, 1959 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 18, Object 6)
      - From Ben Hoberman to Jack Hooke, 1959 August 13 (Box 1, Folder 18, Object 7)
  - Subseries 11: Alan Freed [RESTRICTED], 1943-1960
    Subseries XII: Alan Freed contains documents relating to Alan Freed's payroll, federal tax returns, credit, and banking, including accounting ledgers. Items are arranged chronologically. Some of the items in this subseries are photocopies of original documents.
    Some of the materials in this subseries are confidential and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Redacted access copies of the confidential documents are available in the collection.
    - Payroll record, 1943-1944
      - 1943 February 8-1944 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 20, Object 1)
    - Accounting ledgers, 1954-1960
      - Gross salaries earned, 1954-1958 (Box 1, Folder 21, Object 1-2)
      - Live appearances, 1955 April 5-1960 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 21, Object 3-4)
      - Alan Freed, 1957 July 2-1957 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 21, Object 5-6)
    - Federal tax forms [RESTRICTED], 1958-1959
      Some of the materials in this folder are confidential and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Redacted access copies of the confidential documents are available.
      - Internal Revenue Service Form W-4 [RESTRICTED], 1958 June 3 (Box 5, Folder 1, Object 1-2, Box 1, Folder 22)
        This item is confidential and, therefore, is RESTRICTED. A redacted access copy is available.
      - Internal Revenue Service Form Information Return [RESTRICTED], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 22, Object 3, Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Internal Revenue Service Form W-2 - Copy D for Employer [RESTRICTED], 1958 (Box 5, Folder 1, Object 4, Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Internal Revenue Service Form 1099, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 22, Object 5-6)
      - Internal Revenue Service Form W-2 - Copy D for Employer [RESTRICTED], 1959 (Box 1, Folder 22, Object 7-9, Box 5, Folder 1, Object 5-7)
    - Personal credit and banking, 1955-1957, 1960
      - Saks Fifth Avenue - Mrs. Alan Freed [M. Jacqueline Freed], 1955 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 1-2)
      - Saks Fifth Avenue - Mrs. Alan Freed [M. Jacqueline Freed], 1955 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 3-4)
      - Lord & Taylor - Mrs. Alan Freed [M. Jacqueline Freed], 1955 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 5)
      - Association Credit Bureaus of America Stand Consumer Report - Mr. Alan Freed and Marjorie J., circa 1955 October (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 6-7)
      - Bergdorf Goodman Co. - Mrs. Alan Freed [M. Jacqueline Freed], 1956 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 8-9)
      - Diners' Club membership application, 1956 November 20 (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 10)
      - Security Bank and Trust Company correspondence to The Diners' Club, Incorporated, 1956 December 26 (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 11-12)
      - Bloomingdale’s charges - Mrs. Alan Freed [Marjorie Freed] and Miss Inga Boling, circa 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 13-14)
      - Trade Bank and Trust Company Joint Account Forms - Jack Hooke or Helen Horowitz and Inga or Alan Freed, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 15)
      - Envelope from Trade Bank and Trust Company to the New York City District Attorney's Office – Attention: Mr. Arthur Schwartz, 1960 February (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 16)
      - Note with address of New York City District Attorney's Office, circa 1960 February (Box 1, Folder 23, Object 17)
  - Subseries 12: Firm Amusement Corporation, 1958-1959
    Subseries XI: Firm Amusement Corporation contains cancelled checks. Checks are arranged chronologically.
    - Cancelled checks, 1958 December-1959 January
      - #6595 - Loew's State Theatre account, 1958 December 29 (Box 1, Folder 19, Object 1)
      - #6596 - Loew's State Theatre, 1958 December 30 (Box 1, Folder 19, Object 2)
      - #6597 - Barracuda Music, Inc., 1958 December 30 (Box 1, Folder 19, Object 3)
      - #6997 - Barracuda Music, Inc., 1959 January 2 (Box 1, Folder 19, Object 4)
      - #6600 - Loew's State Theatre account, 1959 January 5 (Box 1, Folder 19, Object 5)
      - #6627 - Barracuda Music, Inc., 1959 January 6 (Box 1, Folder 19, Object 6)
      - #6628 - Marcus Loew Booking Agency, 1959 January 6 (Box 1, Folder 19, Object 7)
  - Subseries 13: Gotham Broadcasting Corporation / WINS, 1954-1961
    Subseries XIII: Gotham Broadcasting Corporation/WINS contains accounting records, correspondence, and an article, flyer, and personnel roster related to Alan Freed and WINS. Items are arranged chronologically. Some of the items in this subseries are photocopies of original documents; some are annotated.
    - Accounting, 1954 December-1958 September
      - Invoice #6595, 1954 December 28 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 1)
      - Invoice #7277, 1955 February 24 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 2)
      - Invoice #2743, 1956 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 3)
      - Invoice #3263, 1956 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 4)
      - Alan Freed/Gotham Broadcasting Corp. charges to advertising and promotion, 1956 October 9-1957 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 5)
      - Alan Freed accounts receivable ledger card WINS/schedule of cash credits, 1956 October 9-1957 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 6)
      - Invoice #3578, 1956 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 7)
      - Invoice #4139, 1956 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 8-10)
      - Invoice #4799, 1957 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 11-12)
      - Invoice #7195, 1957 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 13)
      - Invoice #7275, 1957 March 20 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 14)
      - Invoice #5396, 1957 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 15)
      - Invoice #5400, 1957 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 16)
      - Invoice #5401, 1957 June 7 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 17)
      - Invoice #8625, 1957 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 18)
      - Invoice with inter-office correspondence from Henry G. Kirwan to Alan Freed, 1957 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 19)
      - Invoice #9215, 1957 August 15 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 20-21)
      - Previous billing due, 1957 August 31 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 22)
      - Invoice #9486, 1957 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 23)
      - Invoice #9487, 1957 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 24)
      - Balance due, 1957 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 25)
      - Invoice #7412, 1957 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 26)
      - Invoice #7447, 1957 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 27)
      - Inter-office correspondence from Ivar Quam to Accounting Department, 1958 February 10 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 28)
      - Invoice #14078, 1958 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 24, Object 29-30)
    - Correspondence, 1954 June-1961 August
      - From [Robert Leder?] to Elroy McCaw, 1954 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 1)
      - From [Robert Leder?] to Elroy McCaw, 1954 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 2)
      - From WINS to Alan Freed - exclusive rights agreement, 1954 August 10 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 3-6)
      - From WINS to Alan Freed - syndication and network rights agreement, 1954 August 10 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 7-9)
        Object 8 (signed, original): A2010.1.13
        Object 8 on exhibit. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit for additional information.
      - From Robert J. Leder to Alan Freed - syndication and network rights agreement, 1954 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 10-11)
      - From Robert J. Leder to Alan Freed - syndication and network rights agreement, 1954 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 12)
      - Draft of letter to Alan Freed - syndication and network rights for Gotham-Freed, Inc., 1954 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 13-14)
      - Memo from Frederic A. Johnson to Robert J. Leder, 1954 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 15)
      - From [Robert Leder?] to Elroy McCaw, 1954 November 24 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 16)
      - Inter-Office correspondence from Bob Leder to Elroy McCaw, 1955 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 17)
      - Inter-Office correspondence from Bob Leder to Elroy McCaw, 1955 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 18)
      - Inter-Office correspondence from Bob Leder to Elroy McCaw, 1955 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 19)
      - From Harold Anderson to Edward Davidowitz, 1959 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 20)
      - From Harold Anderson to Edward Davidowitz, 1959 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 21-22)
      - From J. Elroy McCaw to Mary Jane Morris, 1960 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 23)
      - From Anthony V. Soupios to Joseph A. Stone, 1960 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 24)
      - From J. Elroy McCaw to Joseph Stone, 1960 August 6 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 25)
      - From J. Elroy McCaw to Ben F. Waple, 1960 August 6 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 26)
      - Christmas letter for J. Elroy McCaw to Joseph Stone, 1960 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 27)
      - Envelope for Christmas letter from J. Elroy McCaw to Joseph Stone, 1960 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 28)
      - From Federal Communications Commission to Gotham Broadcasting Corporation, 1961 July 6 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 29)
      - From Andrew G. Haley, J. Roger Wollenberg, and Stanley Sporkin to Ben F. Waple, 1961 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 30)
      - From Andrew G. Haley to Ben F. Waple, 1961 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 25, Object 31)
    - Correspondence, 1961 August 8 and 1961 September 6
      - From Andrew G. Haley to Ben F. Waple, 1961 August 8 (Box 1, Folder 26, Object 1)
        Includes attached exhibits.
      - From Andrew G. Haley, J. Roger Wollenberg, and Stanley Sporkin to Ben F. Waple, 1961 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 26, Object 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1954-1959
      - Jablons, Josephine, “'Moondog,' Blues, Jazz Disk Ace Gets N.Y. Show,” The New York Herald Tribune., 1954 September (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 1)
      - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists WINS boycott flyer, circa 1958 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 2)
      - WINS Personnel Roster, 1959 December 28 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 3)
  - Subseries 14: Stamford Productions, 1958-1959
    Subseries XIV: Stamford Productions contains cancelled checks for Stamford Productions. Checks are arranged chronologically.
    - Accounting, 1958 July-1959 December
      - Check #102 – Warren Davis, 1958 July 15 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 1)
      - Check #112 – Gerry Granahan, 1958 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 2)
      - Check #113 – Lillian Briggs, 1958 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 3)
      - Check #115 – Jerry Butler, 1958 August 5 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 4)
      - Check #118 – Curtis Mayfield, 1958 August 5 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 5)
      - Check #122 – Joe Riders, 1958 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 6)
      - Check #123 – Johnnie L. Richardson, 1958 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 7)
      - Check #143 – Renee Minus, 1958 August 12 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 8)
      - Check #144 – Jackie Landry, 1958 August 12 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 9)
      - Check #145 – Sonia Goring, 1958 August 12 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 10)
      - Check #146 – Lois Harris, 1958 August 12 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 11)
      - Check #198 – Jack Scott, 1958 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 12)
      - Check #200 – Herbert Cox, 1958 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 13)
      - Check #202 – Berman Patterson, 1958 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 14)
      - Check #225 – James A. Bowen, 1958 September 21 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 15)
      - Check #251 – Bo Didley, 1958 October 23 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 16)
      - Check #285 – Harvey Fuqua, 1958 October 24 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 17)
      - Check #286 – Prentice Barnes, 1958 October 24 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 18)
      - Check #345 – Beverly Ross, 1958 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 19)
      - Check #383 – Bobby Day, 1959 February 18 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 20)
      - Check #393 – Sandy Stewart, 1959 February 18 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 21)
      - Check #411 – Jerry Vale, 1959 February 18 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 22)
      - Check #462 – Luther Dixon, 1959 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 23)
      - Check #574 – Lenny Renda, 1959 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 24)
      - Trade Bank and Trust Company return notice - return to #67 for check #574, 1959 July (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 25)
      - Check #624 – Dee Clark, 1959 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 26)
      - Trade Bank and Trust Company return notice - return to #67 for check #624, 1959 August (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 27)
      - Check #627 – Stan Robinson, 1959 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 28)
      - Trade Bank and Trust Company return notice - return to #67 for check #627, 1959 August (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 29)
      - Check #688 – Rory Randell, 1959 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 30)
      - Trade Bank and Trust Company return notice - return to #67 for check #688, 1959 September (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 31)
      - Check #752 – Conway Twitty, 1959 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 32)
      - Trade Bank and Trust Company return notice - return to #67 for check #752, 1959 October (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 33)
      - Alan Freed – Big Beat performers' checks (annotated), [1959] December 8 (Box 1, Folder 28, Object 34)
  - Subseries 15: Storz Broadcasting Company, 1962
    - Contract
      - Agreement between Alan Freed and Storz Broadcasting Company, 1962 August 27 (Box 1, Folder 29, Object 1-2)
  - Subseries 16: Superior Records Sales Company, Inc., 1958-1960
    Subseries XVI: Superior Records Sales Company contains cancelled checks. Checks are arranged chronologically with District Attorney's Office information for the Payola trial located at the end.
    - Cancelled checks, 1958 August-1960 April
      - #1834 – Cash, 1958 August 11 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 1)
      - #2035 – Cash, 1958 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 2)
      - #2186 – Cash, 1958 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 3)
      - #2253 – Cash, 1958 December 18 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 4)
      - #2306 – Cash, 1959 January 5 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 5)
      - #2442 – Cash, 1959 February 16 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 6)
      - #2667 – Jack Hooke, 1959 April 28 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 7)
      - #2854 – Inga Boling, 1959 April 28 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 8)
      - #3421 – Cash, 1959 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 9)
      - District Attorney’s Office envelope with Alan Freed/Superior, 1960 February 16 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 10)
      - District Attorney’s Office envelope with Alan Freed/Superior, 1960 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 30, Object 11)
  - Subseries 17: United Artists Records, Inc., 1958-1959, undated
    Subseries XVII: United Artists Records contains cancelled checks and memoranda. Checks are arranged chronologically with other United Artist material at the end. Memoranda are arranged chronologically. Some of the items in this subseries are photocopies of original documents; some are annotated.
    - Cancelled checks, 1958 and undated
      - #447 - R. Kilpatrick, 1958 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 31, Object 1)
      - #617 - R. J. Kilpatrick, 1958 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 31, Object 2)
      - #732 - R. J. Kilpatrick, 1958 July 30 (Box 1, Folder 31, Object 3)
      - #940 - R. J. Kilpatrick, 1958 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 31, Object 4)
      - #1180 - R. J. Kilpatrick, 1958 November 17 (Box 1, Folder 31, Object 5)
      - #1309 - R. J. Kilpatrick, 1958 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 31, Object 6)
      - United Artists envelope: Alan Freed, undated (Box 1, Folder 31, Object 7)
    - Memoranda, 1958 May-1959 September
      - Office Rushgram from Alfred H. Tamarin to Sy Mael, 1958 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 32, Object 1)
      - Office Rushgram from Alfred H. Tamarin to Max E. Youngstein, 1958 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 32, Object 2)
      - Office Rushgram from Kay Norton to Max E. Youngstein, 1958 November 17 (Box 1, Folder 32, Object 3-4)
      - Office Rushgram from Lester Lees to Sy Mael, 1959 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 32, Object 5)
      - Office Rushgram from Lester Lees to Sy Mael, 1959 March 17 (Box 1, Folder 32, Object 6)
      - Office Rushgram from Simon Mael to David Picker, 1959 June 23 (Box 1, Folder 32, Object 7)
      - Office Rushgram from S. Mael to David Picker, 1959 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 32, Object 8)
      - Office Rushgram from S. Mael to Judy, 1959 August 27 (Box 1, Folder 32, Object 9)